<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <root>
    <mail xmlns="http://www.platosys.co.uk/xmail">
        <para>
            <head>Terms and Conditions</head>
            <content>We are glad you want to try Platax, the revolutionary book-keeping system for small enterprises. Our service
                is subject to the terms and conditions set out in in this email. If you accept them, please click on the link at the end to
                confirm your registration; if you don't, then don't click and nothing more will be said about it. The link contains a code that is 
                unique to this application and clicking on it signifies that you agree to these terms. 
            </content>
       </para>
       <para>
           <head>Parties</head>
           <content>This agreement is made between, on the one hand, Platosys Technology (Platosys, we, us), and on the other hand, {name} (you), whose email address is {email}</content>
       </para>
       <para>
           <head>Experimental Software</head>
           <content>Platax is trial software. The service is provided as-is, with no guarantee that it will work, that your data will be secure
               or that Platosys will continue to provide the service. You agree that you use the service at your own risk.  
               We will try to keep it working, to protect your data, and to continue to provide
               the service, but we can make no guarantees. As a trial user, you are contributing to its development and we guarantee that should 
               we ever offer the service on commercial terms we will do so to you at a discount in consideration of your contribution.
           </content>
       </para>
       <para>
           <head>Personal Agreement</head>
           <content>
               This agreement is personal to you as an individual and cannot be assigned. It is additional to and is not replaced by any agreement between Platosys and
               any enterprise represented by you.
           </content>
      </para>
    </mail>
</root>